My child .
My baby .
Finally inside me .
No one will take him from me .
No one can hurt him now .
No one .
Matthieu .
She 's doing just fine .
So , Sarah ...
have you got a name picked out for the baby ?
All right . We 'll admit you tomorrow morning at 7 .
Nothing happens by evening ,
then we can always provoke labor .
Don 't worry , Sarah . It 'll go just fine .
You have someone to bring you here tomorrow morning ?
Usually , we 'd have an ambulance ,
but on Christmas morning , I 'm sure you can- -
Yes , someone 's gonna take me here .
Good .
Thank you , Doctor . I 'll see you tomorrow .
Right .
And enjoy your last night of peace and quiet .
It won 't be long now , huh ?
Hmm ?
Well , I had four kids .
Your first one , I bet .
It 's horrible , the first kid .
In my own case ,
it took 13 hours to deliver it ,
my first baby .
Oh , murder . I mean murder .
I was in such fucking pain .
He put me through all that , but ... he was born dead .
You know very well that smoking 's forbidden here .
Everyone here is so full of shit .
Twat .
I must say , with what 's happening right now ,
I 'm glad you don 't have to work .
It 's really nothing to be freaked out about .
A couple of cars burned .
Well , personally , I feel better with you home
rather than photographing riots .
It freaks me out less .
So , Jean-Pierre seems like a nice man .
Have you and he gotten to be- -
He 's my employer .
That 's too bad .
I was hoping to be introduced one of these days , you know ?
Well , so ...
what do you wanna do ?
Christmas dinner at your house or at mine ?
I 'm not hungry , Louise .
I 'm sick of eating .
We 're going to be all right now .
Look , I need to be alone , Louise .
Go home now , would you , please ?
Hello ?
Yeah ?
What ?
I don 't give a shit that he needs headlines .
I don 't give a shit .
Go ahead and tell him .
Exactly .
Then you get on it and figure something out .
Explain it to the guy .
It 's burning cars and the whole fucking mess on page one .
That 's the headline . Nothing else . Thank you .
Right . No . Nothing .
All right . So long . Merry Christmas .
That fucker makes- -
gets me fucking irritable .
Bloody mess in the burbs
and not one competent man to cover it .
So , sweetheart , how have you been ?
It 's been rough without you out there .
It 's just kids having a blast , 'cause they 're bored .
Yeah .
Meanwhile , cars are burning ,
the cops are on edge ,
my reporters are all duds .
Shitty Christmas , you know ?
So , my place , 6 in the morning ?
- That so ? - Mmm .
I guess that means I better cut my Christmas Eve short
so I don 't keep the pretty lady waiting .
What about you ?
Will you be with your mother tonight ?
I don 't give a shit about Christmas .
I 'd rather be alone .
You won 't say that next year .
I can guarantee that .
No , Louise .
No , don 't bother coming tomorrow .
I told you , I 'll be fine alone .
We 've already been through all that .
So you 'll come by on Monday .
No , Jean-Pierre 's coming to get me .
We just spoke about that , Louise .
I mean , I gave him the keys , yeah .
No. I had enough of this . I 'm gonna turn in .
Horseshit .
I can 't see .
Yeah , who is it ?
Hi . Excuse me for disturbing you on Christmas Eve ,
but I got this problem .
Could I come in to make a quick phone call , please ?
Don 't you have a cell phone ?
My battery 's dead .
What exactly happened ?
My car broke down on the corner .
No . Sorry , but , uh , my husband works .
He 's already gone to bed .
I won 't make any noise . It 'll just be a minute .
I promise .
Please ?
No. I 'm really sorry .
Yeah , look , try , uh- - try another house .
There 's lots of dinners tonight .
Please , it 'll only take a second .
I don 't want to be alone with all this violence .
My husband 's sleeping , I told you !
Your husband 's not sleeping , Sarah .
He 's dead .
What ?
Open the door , Sarah .
Who are you ?
You know my name . How ?
Open the door and you 'll know .
I 'm calling the police , all right ?
Fine . Go fuck yourself .
Hello ?
Look , there 's some strange lady outside my house .
You gotta come really quick .
I can 't imagine what she wants .
She knows my name .
She knows all about me . She ...
I 'm pregnant !
The cops are gonna be here in five minutes .
Get the hell out of here !
Good evening , ma 'am .
Did you call Emergency about an attempted break-in ?
Yeah , that was me . Come on in .
You live alone ?
Yes .
Another guy scared of becoming a dad ?
Not that simple .
And who is this woman ?
I don 't know ,
but she knows my name .
Which is on the letterbox right outside .
All about who I am .
You 're sure it was a woman ?
You get a look at the face , or ...
No . She stuck to the shadows .
I mean , I tried to get a picture ,
but this is all I could get .
Yeah , right .
Not much we can do with that .
Nobody around .
Don 't worry . I 'm sure she left .
Look , I 'm gonna lock you in for the night .
We 'll notify the unit on patrol tonight .
We 've got everyone on duty already , but ...
we 're gonna post a bulletin .
They 'll call around in the course of the night
to make sure you 're okay .
Thanks .
Pretty empty around here for Christmas Eve .
That 's how this neighborhood is .
- Good night , ma 'am . - Bye .
- So long . - Don 't worry . She won 't be back .
Have a good night .
Which has been going on
since last November 27th
and the accidental death of two French citizens
from immigrant families .
Rioting has since spread
throughout underprivileged areas of the Paris suburbs
as well as other major cities .
Mass transit passengers as well as police
and firefighters have been injured .
Over 300 communities have been affected .
4,900 vehicles set ablaze
while scores of businesses , homes and places of worship ...
More than 2,000 immigrants involved in the riots ...
What do you want , you pain in my ass ?
The interior secretary 's inflammatory comments ,
much quoted in the press this morning ,
exasperated an alre- -
Hello. lt 's me again , Jean-Pierre .
Well , look , you 're feeding your face , I guess .
Something pretty weird happened tonight ,
so I was hoping that tomorrow
you could enhance a couple of shots of mine .
Right . See you in the morning .
No !
Sarah ?
Oh , excuse me . I 'm sorry to bother you .
Jean-Pierre Montevant , Sarah 's chief editor .
Sarah 's on the way to- - to my Christmas dinner .
I stopped here to see if she was a bit ,
you know , worried with this suburban violence .
I 'm supposed to pick her up- -
so she left me her keys- -
tomorrow morning .
Anyway , I see her mom got here ... before me .
When a daughter needs , her mother knows .
Right .
Well , so everything 's okay ?
She went to bed an hour ago .
I better get going .
See you later .
Oh , please don 't run off . Will you have a drink ?
I 've been looking forward to meeting you .
Do say yes .
So , Mrs. Scarangelo , looking forward to being a grandmother ?
It took her hours to fall asleep .
Don 't wake her .
Oh , of course .
You 're right . I 'm sorry .
I 'm glad she 's holding up well .
She went through hell after the accident .
Of course , so did I .
These past few months have been awful .
But I know the birth will save us .
Another drink ?
What the hell ?
My little photographer .
Always taking her pictures and leaving them around .
When did she take this one ? Have any idea ?
Because I 'm pretty sure it 's
one of these Sarah called me about .
Really ? What did she have to say ?
Something was bothering her . There was a picture
she wanted to try ...
to enhance .
Enhance ?
I 'm not sure what it 's about . She might have wanted ...
to just enlarge it or to try and clean it up .
Like this face , for example .
Who are you ? What are you doing here ?
Where 's Sarah ?
Maybe you should tell us who you are .
You just barge into somebody 's house ?
Keep your voice down . Sarah 's sleep- -
Where 's my daughter ?
Well , then , who are you ?
Pictures of you .
Sarah ?
Everything all right up there ?
Mom ...
Mommy !
Mommy .
Sarah ?
Help me .
Help me . Help me .
Shit !
Who the fuck are you ?
Open your door .
Open it !
Open the door .
Why me ?
I want one .
What kind of a man would fuck a maniac like you ?
Open it , Sarah !
Don 't be afraid .
You don 't want that child . I 'll take good care of him .
What are you talking about ?
We just stop off to see
if the nice lady is all tucked in , okay ?
Then we 'll take our nightly jackpot winner
to the station ,
Mr. Abdel Shani Asadi .
Abdel Hanusian . You got the wrong guy , man .
I swear . I mean , I 'm not into Molotov cocktails .
Anyway , if I 'm gonna go torch some cars ,
I 'm not so crazy , I 'm gonna have my l.D. in my wallet .
Fuck .
- l wasn 't doing anything . - Quit trying to confuse the issue .
First , we 'll see if Mrs. Scarangelo 's head is on her pillow ,
then we bring this misunderstood child to get booked ,
then we go get his homeys back in the hood .
Can 't let him spend Christmas all alone in the lockup
with nobody else around .
Your friends are out there .
We 're gonna go get them , and you guys can party down .
- l don 't observe it , so fuck Christmas . - Whoa .
Well , hey , right . Doesn 't observe Christmas .
Excuse me . Hello ? How are you , babe ?
Think his girlfriend is such a pain in the balls ?
Maybe . Meantime , he 's in the car with the heat on .
I mean , no . We 're going off duty .
We just gotta check out this woman .
We 'll be back right after , you know ?
Yes , I love you . Come on . Quit it .
Busting your chops , right ?
Wait . Hold on . Shut your face , all right ?
Yeah .
No , I 'm talking to a perp in the car ,
not to you .
Joy to the world
Mrs. Scarangelo , it 's the police .
- Hi . Merry Christmas . - Merry Christmas .
Just stopped by to see if you 're okay .
Our duty log says a woman was harassing you .
No , it 's been hours . I 'm okay .
Don 't hesitate to call us if she comes back .
Yeah , sure .
Excuse me . What 's that noise ?
It 's the spin cycle on my ancient washing machine .
- All right . - Cheaper to run at night , huh ?
- Yeah . - Okay .
- Well , you have a good one . - Right .
- Thanks . - Merry Christmas . So long .
Bye , Officer .
God , a cup of coffee about now .
Hey .
No , I hear you , I hear you .
Did you forget something ?
One stupid detail .
Just wondering what you were gonna name him .
Who ?
Your child .
Watch her .
Holy fuck !
Arrest her ! Arrest her !
Hands behind you ! On the ground ! Fast !
It 's a fucking war zone .
It 's the police .
Don 't move !
All right .
I 'm gonna remove the scissors .
Don 't move .
Open the door ! Open the door !
No ! No !
All right . All right . You can make it .
Open the door .
Open it ! Open the fucking door !
Oh , my fucking God !
Sorry . Gotta go .
You 're gonna have to come along .
- What ? - Something went bad .
That 's police brutality , man .
You 're putting me on a leash like a mutt ?
Put a sock in it and come on .
- Hey , chill out a second . - Move it .
- Officer , let me out of here , please ! - Here , take this .
Let me go !
We gotta get out of this fucking place !
Get the hell in here !
You all right ? All right . Just calm down .
All right ?
It 'll be all right . It 'll be all right .
You , get it together !
It 's fine . I 'll be back in a second .
Just stay there . You . You !
- You know how to use that ? - No .
You arm it here , okay ? And fire .
Yo ! Just point and pull the trigger , okay ?
- Please let me out of this awful place ! - You 're coming with me .
I 'll be right back . Stay here .
- What happened ? Huh ? - ls she gone ?
Yeah , she 's gone .
She went out the window of your bedroom .
She 's still here ! She 's still here !
No , calm down . Calm down . Christ .
You got a circuit breaker ?
Know where it is ?
Look at me , now . Know where it is ?
Downstairs ? All right . Let 's go .
One second . I 'm gonna give you a gun .
Take this . Take it !
Careful . Oh , shit !
Got any bandages ? You got any bandages ?
- There ... - Yes ?
There ? In the drawer ?
Here . Hold this .
Take the flashlight . Hold it up !
I can 't see . Here .
Hold the light up , for Christ sake .
It 's all right . Relax .
- Take off the handcuffs ! - Shut your face !
Hold this , okay ? Hold the light steady .
I have to put the breaker back on , okay ?
Wait for me here .
Hold still .
I killed my mother .
- l killed my mother . - lt 's all right . Calm down now .
Man , we gotta get out of this place !
Shit !
I 'm gonna call for an ambulance and backup from my car , okay ?
You 'll be all right .
All right .
All right . Put this on .
Can you walk ? Yeah ?
Okay , so you 'll wait in the bedroom . Give me your hand .
Give me your hand ! Help her up .
Okay . Can you walk ?
Okay ?
You all right ?
Be right back .
Let 's go . Walk .
Hold the light .
All right . Once I get the lights on , I 'll let you go .
Once you 're outside , find every cop you can .
Hold the fucking light ! There 's nobody here !
Don 't shine it in my eyes !
- Oh , fuck ! - The flashbulb !
- What ? - The flashbulb !
What kind of crap is this ?
Back up .
Back up !
Hey , lady !
Hey , lady ! She 's still here !
Come on ! Get up ! Come on ! Get up !
Fuck !
Where the fuck are your keys ?
Shh , shh , shh , shh , shh , shh .
Sarah .
Where are you hiding , bitch ?
You can kill me again , Sarah .
You already did once .
My child .
My baby .
Finally inside me .
No one will take him from me .
No one can hurt him now .
No one .
They told me that there were no survivors .
Officer ?
The baby 's coming .
The baby !
Shh !
Mommy !
Calm down .
I 'm right here .
Shh , shh , shh , shh .
I think it 's stuck .
- Mommy ! - Shh !
Mommy !
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services , lnc . Burbank , CA